{
    "subject": "Colin_Mochrie",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Debra_McGrath",
    "human_readable": "Colin Mochrie is married to Debra McGrath.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9883117079734802,
            "question": "Is Debra McGrath married to Colin Mochrie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9829320907592773,
            "question": "Who are the spouses of Colin Mochrie and Debra McGrath?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9741061925888062,
            "question": "Is there a marital connection between Colin Mochrie and Debra McGrath?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9221816658973694,
            "question": "Who is Colin Mochrie married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9142574071884155,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Colin Mochrie and Debra McGrath?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8207771182060242,
            "question": "What is the status of Colin Mochrie and Debra McGrath's relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.797409176826477,
            "question": "To whom is Colin Mochrie legally bound in marriage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7411916255950928,
            "question": "What is the name of Colin Mochrie's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6609211564064026,
            "question": "Name the couple where Colin Mochrie is one partner."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5159204006195068,
            "question": "Who is Colin Mochrie's partner in life?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Colin Mochrie is married to Debra McGrath.",
            "html": "yago_4045_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name the couple where Colin Mochrie is one partner.",
            "html": "yago_4045_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Colin Mochrie's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_4045_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To whom is Colin Mochrie legally bound in marriage?",
            "html": "yago_4045_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4045_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4045_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4045_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4045_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4045_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4045_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4045_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4045_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4045_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4045_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can confidently say that:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`\n\nHere's why:\n\n* There are multiple documents confirming Colin Mochrie's marriage to Debra McGrath. (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_4045/re-ranker-msmarco/20.txt, 77.txt, 16.txt)\n* The information consistently mentions that they got married in 1989 and have been together for over 35 years.\n* There is no conflicting evidence to suggest otherwise.\n\nSo, according to the documents provided, Colin Mochrie is indeed married to Debra McGrath."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Colin Mochrie is currently married to Debra McGrath, and provide details about their marriage beginning in 1989."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}